MICHAL ZADARNOWSKI WEB DEVELOPER

michal.zadarnowski@gmail.com • +447480221301 • Paisley website: zetdotcom.github.io

PERSONAL PROFILE

"To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work" (Sister Mary Lauretta)

Believing in the above quote I have decided to change my career from being an Accountant to become a successful Web Developer. Web programming and learning modern technologies has become my passion and I continue to develop my skills every day. Experienced in contact with clients and providing excellent quality work on time. Strong organisational and IT skills allowed me to work out solutions to complete most of the jobs within 80% of the budgeted time.

SKILLS & TECHNOLOGIES















HTML5



(0((

BOOTSTRAP



JAVASCRIPT





ECMASCRIPT 6



AJAX/JSON



DEOC







IN PROGRESS...









- Excellent interpersonal skills and the ability to communicate effectively at any level.
- The ability to work efficiently under pressure and to tight deadlines.
- Reliable, responsible and able to work under minimum supervision.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Freelance Front-End Developer - (October 2017 – present) PROJECTS examples:

Local Church Community website (www.jezuszyje.co.uk)

- HTML5, CSS3, JS, REACT, FIREBASE
- Working alongside two other developers to create functional, accessible website for community counting
 around 150 people. The site includes automatically updating google calendar, gallery fetching photos from
 Facebook profile, YouTube videos and study materials for participants.
- My responsibilities: design UI/UX, code presentational components, website maintenance and updates.

Matt Wielunski Personal Trainer (no domain bought yet- check zetdotcom.github.io projects section)

(website still in progress)

- HTML5, CSS3, JS, REACT, GATSBY.JS, WP REST API
- Static site generated by Gatsby.js which pulls backend data from WordPress using WP REST API.
- Advantages of static site: more secure, faster, less maintenance, Progressive Web App possibility.
- Website automatically rebuilds and deploys when a post is added or updated.

Electric Map (https://electric-map-1515938108302.firebaseapp.com)

- HTML5, CSS3, JS, REACT, GOOGLE MAPS API
- Web application showing electric car charging point across the UK pulling data from JSON file.

SMG Learning – (https://zetdotcom.github.io/smg-learning)

- HTML5, CSS3, GATSBY.JS, REACT
- Contract job to translate one-page PSD into functional website for client presentation.

(for more projects check my website: zetdotcom.github.io)

EDUCATION

edX - University of Pennsylvania – Online Learning Programming for the Web with JavaScript April 2018 – present

Glasgow Caledonian University
BA (Hons) Accountancy- (2.1 degree)

September 2011 – May 2014

Reid Kerr College, Paisley
HNC & HND Accounting (grades A)

August 2009 - June 2011

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

John M Taylor & Co (January 2016 - present)

Accounts Assistant

- Financial Statements preparation
- Provided assistance to colleagues with Microsoft Excel related issues
- Effectively communicated with other departments and with clients

DA Accountants (November 2014 – April 2015) & French Duncan LLP (April 2015 – January 2016)

Accounts Assistant

- Responsible for full life cycle of accounts preparation from requesting the records from clients up to handing in final draft to the manager.
- During the period of changes in the company used and quickly learned few different accounting software packages what prevented big delays in delivery of the service to the clients.
- Managed workload, prioritised jobs to make sure they are completed on time.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Provided private lessons for Higher Maths students as well as Year 1 Accountancy students.
- Designed t-shirts for my church community.
- Designed and produced leaflets for relatives' business which resulted in sales increase.
- Co-ordinator of Men's Group in my community.
- Table Tennis enthusiast